[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Malek_s02_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95A_Main_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s01_05",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "s02_Quest_MediumHands",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "@95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Marauder",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Marauder_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Malek_s02_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95A_Main_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s01_05",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "s02_Quest_MediumHands",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "@95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Syndicate",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Syndicate_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Malek_s02_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95A_Main_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s01_05",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "s02_Quest_MediumHands",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "@95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_GlimpseofthePast",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95A_S02_GlimpseofthePast_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Sadiki_s02_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95A_Main_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_GlimpseofthePast_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
        "ItemRewardQty": 2,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "@95A_S02_GlimpseofthePast_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@95A_S02_GlimpseofthePast_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_GlimpseofthePast_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95A_S02_GlimpseofthePast_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95A_S02_GlimpseofthePast_Obj_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_WordofaThief",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95A_S02_WordofaThief_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Sharif_s02_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95A_Main_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_WordofaThief_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "s02_Quest_Ring",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "@95A_S02_WordofaThief_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@95A_S02_WordofaThief_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_WordofaThief_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95A_S02_WordofaThief_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95A_S02_WordofaThief_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95A_S02_WordofaThief_Obj_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_HardBoiled",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95A_S02_HardBoiled_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Grace_s02_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95A_Main_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_HardBoiled_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "s02_Quest_1hTowerShield",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "@95A_S02_HardBoiled_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@95A_S02_HardBoiled_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_HardBoiled_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95A_S02_HardBoiled_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95A_S02_HardBoiled_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95A_S02_HardBoiled_Obj_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Grace_s02_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95A_Main_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "s02_SatyrFlute",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "@95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_Obj_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_SecondThoughts",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95A_S02_SecondThoughts_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Grace_s02_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95A_Main_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_05",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_SecondThoughts_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "s02_Quest_MediumFeet",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "@95A_S02_SecondThoughts_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@95A_S02_SecondThoughts_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_SecondThoughts_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95A_S02_SecondThoughts_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95A_S02_SecondThoughts_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95A_S02_SecondThoughts_Obj_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_FalseProfits",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95A_S02_FalseProfits_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Grace_s02_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95A_Main_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_06",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_FalseProfits_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "UmbralShardT1",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1000,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "@95A_S02_FalseProfits_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@95A_S02_FalseProfits_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_FalseProfits_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95A_S02_FalseProfits_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95A_S02_FalseProfits_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95A_S02_FalseProfits_Obj_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_EggHunt",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95A_S02_EggHunt_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Zander_s02_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95A_Main_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_07",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_EggHunt_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "s02_Quest_2hFireStaff",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "@95A_S02_EggHunt_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@95A_S02_EggHunt_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_EggHunt_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95A_S02_EggHunt_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95A_S02_EggHunt_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95A_S02_EggHunt_Obj_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_PrecariousPosition",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95A_S02_PrecariousPosition_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Sharif_s02_06",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95A_Main_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_08",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_PrecariousPosition_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "s02_Quest_MediumLegs",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "@95A_S02_PrecariousPosition_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@95A_S02_PrecariousPosition_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_PrecariousPosition_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95A_S02_PrecariousPosition_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95A_S02_PrecariousPosition_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95A_S02_PrecariousPosition_Obj_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_HeiroftheSands",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95A_S02_HeiroftheSands_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Sharif_s02_07",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95A_Main_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_09",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_HeiroftheSands_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "s02_Quest_1hSword",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "@95A_S02_HeiroftheSands_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@95A_S02_HeiroftheSands_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_HeiroftheSands_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95A_S02_HeiroftheSands_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95A_S02_HeiroftheSands_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95A_S02_HeiroftheSands_Obj_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_EmptyNest",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95A_S02_EmptyNest_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Rima_s02_04",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95A_Main_11",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_10",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_EmptyNest_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "s02_Quest_MediumHead",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "@95A_S02_EmptyNest_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@95A_S02_EmptyNest_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_EmptyNest_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95A_S02_EmptyNest_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95A_S02_EmptyNest_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95A_S02_EmptyNest_Obj_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_BreakSomeEggs",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95A_S02_BreakSomeEggs_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Sharif_s02_11",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95A_Main_12",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_11",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_BreakSomeEggs_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "s02_Quest_MediumChest",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "@95A_S02_BreakSomeEggs_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@95A_S02_BreakSomeEggs_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_BreakSomeEggs_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95A_S02_BreakSomeEggs_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95A_S02_BreakSomeEggs_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95A_S02_BreakSomeEggs_Obj_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_LegacyoftheSands",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95A_S02_LegacyoftheSands_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Grace_s02_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95A_Main_13",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_12",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_LegacyoftheSands_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "s02_Quest_2hGreatsword",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "@95A_S02_LegacyoftheSands_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@95A_S02_LegacyoftheSands_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_LegacyoftheSands_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95A_S02_LegacyoftheSands_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95A_S02_LegacyoftheSands_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95A_S02_LegacyoftheSands_Obj_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_Remembrance",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95A_S02_Remembrance_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Grace_s02_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95A_Main_14",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_13",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_Remembrance_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "House_HousingItem_Season2_SandwormEgg_Variant3",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "@95A_S02_Remembrance_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@95A_S02_Remembrance_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_Remembrance_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95A_S02_Remembrance_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95A_S02_Remembrance_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95A_S02_Remembrance_Obj_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95A_T01_RiseoftheBeast",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95A_S02_T1_RiseoftheBeast_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Phaedra_s02_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95A_Trial_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_14",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_T01_RiseoftheBeast_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "s02_Quest_2hBow",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "@95A_T01_RiseoftheBeast_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@95A_T01_RiseoftheBeast_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_T01_RiseoftheBeast_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95A_T01_RiseoftheBeast_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95A_T01_RiseoftheBeast_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95A_T01_RiseoftheBeast_Obj_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95A_T02_RiseoftheHero",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95A_S02_T2_RiseoftheHero_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Phaedra_s02_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Trial_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_T02_RiseoftheHero_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "TRUE",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "@95A_T02_RiseoftheHero_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@95A_T02_RiseoftheHero_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_T02_RiseoftheHero_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95A_T02_RiseoftheHero_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95A_T02_RiseoftheHero_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95A_T02_RiseoftheHero_Obj_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    }
]
